Guide to the George Lincoln Burr papers,1861-1942.
Burr, George Lincoln papers, 1886-1942
- Series II. Personal Documents and Cornell Material
  - Kleiner Beitrag zur Geschichte des Hexenwesens, transcribed by Burr (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Dietrich Flade notes by Burr (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Savonarola notes (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Drafts on witchcraft history (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Degrees and Medals (Box 39)
  - Research Papers by Students (Box 40)
  - Research Papers by Students (Box 41)
  - Jan. 5, "1970 Accession: typed and printed items concerning the AHA-Bancroft episode, 1915; bibliographical notes (witchcraft). (Box 42)
- Series III. Photographs and drawings
  - George Lincoln Burr caricature in A.D. White library by Herbert Roland Bainton, circa 1940-1943 (Box M.S. box, Folder 1)
    Formerly on display in the A.D. White library
  - Cyanotype and blueprint of Sigma Phi and Professor Nichols house (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Edna Moffatt (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Schilliger (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Burr-Nelson and Morse-Nelson, 1920s-1930s (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Cabinet cards, 1800s-early 1900s (Box 28, Folder 4)
    Including Isabelle Robertson, Frances Boynton, Margaret Boynton, Mary Bartlett Hill, Emma Berry, Stella Spencer, Mrs. Clarke, Winifred Ball, and other Cornell students and associates
  - Cartes-de-Visite and other small photographs, 1800s-early 1900s (Box 28, Folder 5)
    Including Lottie Stines, Martha Whilson, Fran Fanny Stadeli, Amelia Shapleigh, Emily Outwater, and others
  - People, including Bobbie Stert, Winifred Ball and others, early 1900s-1930s (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Leipzig (Box 28, Folder 7-8)
    Including Anna Biedermann, Therese Biedermann, Mrs. Karl Biedermann, Ludwig Knorr, and history professors
  - Cornell faculty (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Photographs of the Burr's, labelled "to use" with chapter numbers and a sketch (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Scenes and Buildings (Box 28, Folder 11)
    Taughannock, Cornell library (1890s), AE Kent and Co, Richmond from Manchester
  - Telluride group photos, Cornell History Club (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Large group photos (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Large Cornell women group photos (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Van Loon photos and sketches (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Unidentified people (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Large photos, Early 1900s (Box 28, Folder 17)
    Including Lyman Abbott, Evan Evans, Edward Huhur, Agnes Tierney
  - George Lincoln Burr, Late 1800s-1930s (Box 29, Folder 1-3, 10)
  - Matsy Martin (Mrs. G.L. Burr) (Box 29, Folder 4-5)
  - Cabinet cards, Late 1800s (Box 29, Folder 6)
    Including Isabel Howland, Harriet Day, Hannah Otis, Phebe Fort, Alice Goddard (1881), Clara Teague, Mary Putnam, and Gertrude van Pelt and others
  - Cabinet cards, Late 1800s (Box 29, Folder 7)
    Including FJ Scott (1880), FC Whitney, Frank Leverance, LF Boyer, George Schurman, Ostrander, Fred Kilborne and others
  - Cabinet cards, Late 1800s (Box 29, Folder 8)
    Including Herrick, Halsey, Hahn, Concklin, Curtice, Clarke, Wightman, Stearns, Holmes, Hoyt, Hough, Wing, David Halsey (1881), and Theobald Smith
  - George Lincoln Burr in the AD White library and at his desk (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Cabinet card photos of Burr taken at the Hague, 1896 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Bound photographs, 1902 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    Including Watkins Glen, Taughannock falls and point, Rocky point, South of Sheldrake, Burr on Cayuga Lake, Esty point
  - The Burr family, Late 1800s (Box 29, Folder 13)
    Including Mrs. Andrew Burr, Mrs. WJ Burr, WJ Burr, Sarah Burr, and unidentified
  - Burr family home in Newark Valley and WJ Burr, 1890s (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Dr. Robert Collyer and unidentified, 1910 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Cornell Debating Club, 1881 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Group photos (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Cartes-de-visite (Box 29, Folder 17)
    Including Melville Landon, Harry Norman, Cornelia Smith, DE Roberts, Robina Smith, Albert Jonas, Jonah Walsh, Mary Roberts, and Mrs. RW Walsh
  - Glass slide from drawing (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Sketch of Burr (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Daguerreotype of WJ Burr, 1850 (Box 29, Folder 22)